englishpage.com 2006-11-11

# Privacy Statement

####  Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Englishpage.com logs IP addresses and browser types for systems administration purposes and these logs will be analyzed to constantly improve the value of the materials available on the website. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

####  Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While Englishpage.com does not collect cookies, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

####  Registration Forms

Our site's _Dont' Have a Cow_ registration form requires users to give us their email address. Contact information from the registration forms is used for our weekly newsletter. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

####  Surveys

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address).

####  External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **English Page** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

####  Special Relationships

Englishpage.com contains information provided by other companies and services: 

*This site, **English Page** , uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>. 

* **English Page** has ads served onto out site by Burst Media . To visit their privacy statement, [please click here](http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp). 

* **English Page** has ads served onto out site by Advertising.com . To visit their privacy statement, [please click here](http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html). 

* **English Page** has ads served onto out site by Commission Junction . 

* **English Page** has ads served onto out site by Direct Leads . To visit their privacy statement, [please click here](http://www.directleads.com/privacy.html). 

* News articles appearing in Englishpage.com's _Frontpage Headlines_ are provided by Excite.com. To visit their privacy statement, [please click here](http://www.excite.com/privacy_policy/). 

* The _Questions Page_ bulletin board is provided by 321website.com. Information submitted on the bulletin board is in accordance with the privacy policy of 321website.com. 

* The _Discussions Page_ bulletin board is provided by 321website.com. Information submitted on the bulletin board is in accordance with the privacy policy of 321website.com. 

* The _Recommended Books Page_ bulletin board is provided by 321website.com. Information submitted on the bulletin board is in accordance with the privacy policy of 321website.com. 

* The email capture for our _Don't Have a Cow_ newsletter is provided by 321website.com. Information submitted is not shared with 321website.com, but remains in accordance with the privacy policy of 321website.com. 

* **English Page** is an Amazon.com affiliate member. The Englishpage.com Bookstore links to Amazon.com. Purchases made at Amazon.com are in accordance with the privacy policy of Amazon.com. To visit their privacy statement, [please click here](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/subst/misc/policy/privacy.html/104-8162547-8705216). 

* **English Page** is a Zmedia Affiliate member. The Englishpage.com _Newsletters Page_ automatically submits requests to Zmedia.com. Sign ups are in accordance with the privacy policy of Zmedia.com. 

* **English Page** is a Searchtraffic.com affiliate member. The Englishpage.com _Web Portal_ search box was provided by Searchtraffic.com.

####  Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

####  Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

####  Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us .   
You can send email to [webmaster@englishpage.com](mailto:webmaster@englishpage.com)
